[{"answer": "It shuts off automatically", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No.  They all do", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What's that noise", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "The locks", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Thirty", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It's safe", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The blast?  Honey, I have survived a host of things. Like the song say", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "\"Hell up here", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "For how long?  We've just about run out of everything", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " No, my friend.  We're not going to make do.  Not me!  Not Adam.  We're going up no matter what!  We deserve it. Even if it's terrible", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Are you all right", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "All in yellow?  Oh!  That was my father", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What?  What is it?", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The sky?  Where", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Say what?", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " I do alright", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, your business must not be sports memorabilia, because this one my friend card right her", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, you get out of here", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "We? I'm going home. And, judging by that coat, I'd say you have to get back to the barber college", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You're lost", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I came on a bus", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I don't know. Why doesn't it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " So far", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What is it?", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Good evening. I want to stay at this hotel", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A card", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I was able to get some change downstairs and my father taught me that it's customary to tip in a situation such as this", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "My father is a genius", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Thirt", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "How old do I look", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I guess living up here makes people look older", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Yes. Up here on the fifteenth floor. Goodnight", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "The eyes.  Okay. An ey", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Hey, no kidding?  In color", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why would someone need twenty yacht batteries", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "And who does he work for?  The that place", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Then forget it", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "This is for me", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I don't want to be alone", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Bites what", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Sure", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Everybody knows that. Ask my divorced sisters. Or ask my divorced mom and dad", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Everybody knows that. Ask my divorced sisters. Or ask my divorced mom and dad", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Everybody's divorced", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You almost got us killed", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Never drive again", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You said it would be easy", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Is this your house", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.  It would probably kill him", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yes. He likes windows", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Who are you?", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "It's the mother!", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I'm sorry. But if the shoe fits", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "I see", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Tu parle my friend? Tu a un tres bon accent", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "that place!! La ville de lumieres! C'est bien rencontrer quelqu'un pour pratiquer le francais", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "No, I'm not! My mom taught me", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "She is a dancer! And a lovely one! You would like her very much! Shall we dance", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "What's that mean", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Who did he leave with", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Where are you going", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "To bed", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Exactly! I thought a gentleman was somebody who owned horses. Turns out, the short and very simple definition of a gentleman or a lady i", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "From the oddest place. His parent's told him. I don't think I got that memo", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Give it back to him", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "We'll find him", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Blast-from-the-Past_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "We can make this work, my friend! Believe me! I'm very good at making things work", "qsentId": 70}]